LEE JAE-IN, KIM WOO-SEOK, CHOI YE-BIN
CHA WOO-MIN, AN JI-HO, JUNG SO-RI
SCRIPTWRITER: KANG MIN-JI
DIRECTOR: IM DAE-WOONG
NIGHT HAS COME
ALL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, LOCATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHA YU-JUN IS A DOCTOR
What's this?
I'm a Citizen.
- What about you?
- I'm...
YOU CAN SELECT 1 PARTICIPANT
AND USE YOUR HEAL SKILL
THE SELECTED PARTICIPANT WILL BE
PROTECTED FROM THE MAFIA'S ATTACK
WILL YOU USE IT ON CHA YU-JUN?
YES
HEAL SKILL USED ON CHA YU-JUN
Ji-soo.
THE SELECTED PARTICIPANT WILL BE
PROTECTED FROM THE MAFIA'S ATTACK
YOU CAN REVIVE SOMEONE
WHO WAS VOTED FOR AND EXECUTED
No.
WILL YOU USE IT ON PARK JI-SOO?
48 HOURS HAVE NOT YET PASSED
SINCE YOU LAST USED HEAL
ADHERE TO THE COOLDOWN TIME
What's this?
Ji-soo.
I don't want to die.
You won't die.
I'll never let you die.
We should go home.
Don't you want to go home?
I do.
It's me.
I'm the Mafia.
It's not you.
It's really not you.
Don't.
It's not him!
Don't do it!
HEAL SKILL USED ON KIM JUN-HEE
Hey.
Take it back.
Say you're not the Mafia!
EPISODE 8
Did you find the photo album?
It's not on the first floor.
No.
I swear it was here.
It must be somewhere.
Let's keep looking.
Cha Yu-jun...
- ...has died.
- Yu-jun?
- Cha Yu-jun was...
- Why?
...the Doctor.
All participants,
identify the Mafia and begin to vote.
He didn't break any rules.
So why did he...
Did he fall?
He didn't fall.
Someone killed him.
There are lots of signs of a struggle,
and there are wounds on his head.
Someone attacked him.
I bet it was the Mafia.
I don't know.
Even if it was, this is wrong.
How could they kill during the day?
What will you do now?
Find out who did it.
Why do you think Yu-jun was here?
Yoon-seo.
The Mafia are insane.
They're killing during the day now?
Even if Yu-jun was the Doctor,
this is too much.
Let's just catch the darn Mafia.
Who on earth is it?
Darn it.
- Hey, guys.
- What?
- Come over here.
- What for?
What's this?
What is it?
KIM JUN-HEE IS THE MAFIA
JIN DA-BEOM IS THE MAFIA
FROM THE POLICE
Jun-hee...
...and you are the Mafia?
No.
I'm really not part of the Mafia.
Guys, I'm not.
I'm a Citizen.
Who wrote this and why?
It's really not me.
The Police used their Skill twice.
I think it makes sense that it's two.
But earlier it said Jun-hee was a Citizen.
I'm not part of the Mafia either.
Don't lie.
I bet the Police wrote this
because the last one was a lie.
Right.
The real Police would name the Mafia.
Why would they name a Citizen?
No.
This could be fake.
It's weird how it
appeared right after Yu-jun died.
The person who killed him...
...could've written this
to frame them as the Mafia.
You guys.
Why did you get here so late?
Didn't you write this?
If so, Yoon-seo wouldn't have said
what she just did.
What on earth is this anyway?
JUN-HEE IS A CITIZEN
FROM THE POLICE
Police.
Quit all this and show yourself.
Show your phones.
Let's see your Skills.
There's no need to do that.
The person who killed Yu-jun.
I think I know who it is.
You said you'd tell us who did it.
Why did you bring us here?
In the warehouse...
...I found a footprint.
And this was next to it.
I think it's from the shoe
of Yu-jun's killer.
This is the same one.
It stood out because I found it
weird there was a blank.
I think this explains it.
This is an accessory
lots of basketball shoes have.
Basketball shoes?
What?
Is this yours?
Why would you say that, you wench?
Show us your shoes so we can check.
I don't use that, okay?
Let's see and find out.
Take a look then.
It's not his.
I told you so.
What?
It's really not me.
Why suspect me?
If you're innocent, show us, then.
- Yes, let's see.
- It's not me.
It's not me!
Will you stop it?
Darn it.
Who bit you?
It really was you.
Why did you do it?
It wasn't me.
I didn't kill him.
We found the weapons you used.
Don't try to lie.
Darn it.
Shall I tell the truth?
Go Kyung-jun killed him.
It wasn't me!
What are you saying, psycho?
The shoe and brick says it's you!
How do you know that?
We never mentioned a brick.
How did you know about it?
What?
Jin-ha was with someone else
in the warehouse.
We found another identical footprint
but without the heel pad.
It was you, wasn't it?
Go Kyung-jun.
Guys.
It really wasn't me.
He killed Yu-jun.
He killed Seung-bin too.
You have that darn ax too.
You lunatic.
You fool.
- Take this.
- Hey!
- Darn it.
- Stop it!
- Will you stop?
- Get your hands off me!
You killed him, you dirtbag.
Let go.
I said let go of me.
Kyung-jun!
Will you all get off me?
You lunatic!
Hey.
Let go.
Stay away from me.
You scumbag!
Jun-hee!
Come at me!
I'll take you on!
Get off me!
Come and get me!
Darn it!
I'm okay.
Hey.
What's that?
What a mess.
Did you write it with this?
And you still say he's not the Mafia?
When he wrote all that?
What's this?
Did you name them as the Mafia?
No.
I didn't write it.
Guys, wait.
Don't do anything.
I don't know what's going on!
- Honestly.
- We have the answer.
Vote already.
Hey, Jun-hee.
It wasn't me.
You're the class president!
I don't know what's happening.
Please, Jung-won.
What a joke.
I'm innocent.
He's 100 percent the Mafia!
Let's vote and be done with it!
Will you stop it?
You killed Yu-jun too.
We'll vote at 11 p.m.
You two should wait in a room.
Don't leave the room.
Is this a prison cell?
What?
- Hand over the keys.
- Why?
What if you get out?
How are we to know you won't kill again?
We'll all use the cafeteria now.
Hand over the keys.
They're gone. I lost them.
Don't lie.
Hand them over already.
I don't have them, okay?
Then give me your phone.
I'll keep that as collateral.
You can't go anywhere without your phone.
You murdered someone.
It's the least you can do
to make us trust you.
What on earth, Da-beom?
You'll get it back at voting time.
Guys.
I really am not the Mafia.
I didn't kill Seung-bin.
Don't vote for me, okay?
I really am not the Mafia.
I'm a Citizen.
I must live if you're to live.
This is the men's room.
I know that.
- What?
- Where do you think...
...is the safest place here?
What do you mean?
Speak up.
Where is it?
I don't know.
What a moron.
It's the cafeteria.
- The cafeteria?
- Yes.
No ax can get through the shutters.
So what?
What do you mean "so what?"
Kyung-jun's keys.
Let's take them from him.
We'll let you in.
Join us.
- Did it hurt?
- I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thanks.
If you're done, let's go.
They'll suspect us of being late again.
Okay.
Let's go.
POVIDONE
FROM THE POLICE
KIM JUN-HEE IS MAFIA
JIN DA-BEOM IS THE MAFIA
Now we really have to vote.
What do you want to do?
Anyway,
Kyung-jun seems to be a Citizen.
But we don't know about Jin-ha yet.
Then...
...it's right to save Kyung-jun.
But Kyung-jun is weird too.
Why did he kill the Doctor
if he was a Citizen?
Right.
He had an ax too.
Are you stupid?
He had the keys.
Why would he break the door?
Do you have a hole in your head?
He must've broken it not to be suspected.
You're clueless.
No.
Jin-ha is weirder.
He wrote the others' names
as if he were a Police.
Right.
Jin-ha often borrowed money from Ju-won...
...to buy lottery tickets too.
He might've killed him
because he didn't want to pay him back.
That must be the reason.
Yoon-seo.
Who do you think is the Mafia?
Actually, something is bothering me.
What is it?
When the Mafia kills someone,
it says they're "executed."
But why did it say Yu-jun has "died?"
It's probably because
he died in the daytime.
But what if...
...both Jin-ha and Kyung-jun are Citizens?
What are you going to do then?
Why do you make it so complicated?
The two killed Yu-jun together.
Just...
...tell them not to vote.
No.
If we kill everyone like that,
we're no different from them.
Yes.
Stop saying nonsense.
The Police should use their Skill.
Then out of the two,
we can save the one who is a Citizen.
Right.
That's a safe way to do it.
No.
After the Doctor died,
the Police would be under
even bigger pressure now.
Don't force them.
There is that message too.
That's why it became more complicated.
That's enough.
Let's decide who to vote for first.
Then all of us...
...agree with it,
right?
But...
...what do we do about this?
We should bring it to them.
We should tell them
about the results as well.
Then...
...who should go?
Are we all going?
I'll go.
You guys should hide after voting.
When everyone is hiding,
I'll give the phones to them.
I'll go with you.
We should give these to each of them.
Take it.
Go Kyung-jun, you scumbag.
WILL YOU VOTE FOR GO KYUNG-JUN?
KIM JIN-HA VOTED FOR GO KYUNG-JUN
How about you?
Did you vote?
Please.
KIM JUN-HEE, KIM SO-MI,
CHOI MI-NA, IM EUN-CHAN,
NAM YEON-WOO,
OH JUNG-WON, JIN DA-BEOM,
AHN NA-HEE, LEE YOON-SEO
VOTED FOR KIM JIN-HA
KIM JIN-HA VOTED FOR GO KYUNG-JUN
Please.
Jun-hee.
I'm serious.
It's really not me.
I'm really a Citizen!
Please save me just once.
I really don't want to die.
- Jun-hee, please.
- Jin-ha.
Yu-jun must've wanted to live too.
Please.
KIM JUN-HEE IS MAFIA
JIN DA-BEOM IS THE MAFIA
FROM THE POLICE
This is why you should've gotten insurance.
What did you say?
Never mind.
Tell them to bring my phone.
We didn't bring your phone.
Tell us where the keys are.
I'll give it to you then.
You scumbag.
Have you lost your mind?
You will never find it by yourself.
You know what happens when you can't vote.
Where are the keys?
Da-beom, you've grown a lot.
Right?
You know how to threaten me now.
Follow me.
We don't have time.
Go.
What?
It's not here.
Are you happy now?
Give me my phone now.
You should've told me you needed the keys.
You scared me for no reason.
Where is it?
Over there.
You bring it.
How would I know if it's real or not?
Do whatever you want.
I'm leaving.
I told you to bring it, you scumbag.
We don't have time.
Will you be okay?
Darn it.
Having fun, you piece of trash?
Hey, open it.
Open it, you scumbag!
Open the freaking door!
Open it, you jerk!
Hey, open it!
Open the darn door!
Jin Da-beom, you piece of trash!
I'll kill you when I go out, you rascal!
Open the darn door!
Darn it.
Jin Da-beom!
Open the darn door!
Darn it.
Open it, you scumbag!
Darn it!
Voting is over.
Kim Jin-ha who got
the most votes will be executed.
Darn it.
CLEANING TOOLS
No!
Kim Jin-ha was a Citizen.
What?
Jin-ha was a Citizen.
He was a Citizen?
Darn it.
We're doomed.
I'm going to kill
those darn Mafias tomorrow.
I'll kill you, you piece of trash.
What does it feel
like to be fooled by a loser?
It sucks, doesn't it?
Kyung-jun.
The Mafias...
...choose a target by unanimous consent.
They're all coming.
You scumbag!
Gosh.
You jerk.
You're a piece of trash.
Just die!
Darn it!
Time is up, you idiot!
That really hurt.
You piece of trash.
What?
Get lost!
Darn it.
That really scared me.
Kyung-jun.
They say when people die,
hearing is the last sense to go.
Think about me while listening to this.
NIGHT HAS COME
THIS CONTENT WAS PRODUCED THROUGH...
GWANGJU INFORMATION AND CONTENT AGENCY'S...
2022 OTT PLATFORM CONTENT
PRODUCTION BUSINESS.
Ripped by YoungJedi